dynamicbusiness.com.au 2007-06-18

# DBC-web site design, ebusiness application development, flash design, web consulting, web content management, corporate web site design, ebusiness consultant, web site usability, web programming, web design brisbane, cdrom,dvd,extranet

Dynamic Business Communications Pty Limited have a firm commitment to privacy in accordance with the Privacy Amendment (Private Sector) Act 2000, which took effect in December 2001.

This privacy policy covers all personal information that we hold.

**Collection of information**

Whenever we collect personal information from you we will do so in a lawful and fair way. We will also advise you how and where to contact us.

If we collect the information from a third party we will take reasonable steps to advise you of that collection promptly.

We will tell you why we are collecting the information and the third parties to whom we usually disclose that information.

If you do not wish to provide the information we request, we will tell you what impact this will have.

**Disclosing information**

We will only disclose personal information in accordance with the Act. This means that it will be disclosed if:

We told you when collecting it that it would be disclosed for that purpose or for a related purpose that you would reasonably expect;   
we have your consent; it is part of business assets which we are selling; we are required by law to disclose it; or it is otherwise permitted under the Act 

**Quality of information**

We will take reasonable steps to ensure that the information that we collect, use and disclose is accurate, complete and up to date.

**Security**

We are committed to protecting your privacy and will take reasonable steps to ensure that the information we collect is protected from loss and misuse and from unauthorised access, modification and disclosure. 

**Access to the information we hold**

You can access your personal information upon request. However, there are occasions when this access may be denied under the exemptions contained in the Act.

**Availability of policy**

This policy is available upon request. It will be reviewed from time to time and any amendments will be included in the updated policy.

**Privacy inquiries**

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, any privacy related dealings with us or a possible breach of your privacy or would like further information about our information management practices, you can contact:

Wernher Pramschufer  
Dynamic Busisness Communications Pty Limited   
15, Hindmarsh Place, Westlake  
BRISBANE QLD 74

Phone 07 3376 0333

Fax   07 3878 9573

Email: [wernher@dynamicbusiness.com.au](mailto:iwernher@dynamicbusiness.com.au)
